(Sheldon:)...exhausted by your constant tomfoolery.
(Raj:)But it's true.
[SNORTS]
(Raj:)We put all your vital information
into this dating site...
...answered all questions like you would
and they found a match for you.
(Raj:)-Her name is Amy Farrah Fowler.
-Please.
(Sheldon:)Even assuming you could answer
any question the way I would...
(Sheldon:)...the algorithms used
by matchmaking sites are complete hokum.
That's the answer
we gave to the question.
"What is your attitude
towards online dating?"
Well, Howard wanted to write
"mumbo jumbo," but I said no.
Our Sheldon would say "hokum."
(Leonard:)Come on,
where's your scientific curiosity?
Most of it is being applied to unraveling
secrets of universe...
...while the rest of it is wondering why
I'm having this conversation with you.
Okay, how about this?
(Raj:)Even Spock had a date
once every seven years.
(Sheldon:)He didn't date. It was pon farr.
(Sheldon:)His blood boiled with mating lust.
(Howard:)Why don't you start
with a cup of coffee...